# FERNANDA CHAVES feefachaaves@gmail.com | 07902421194

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Fernanda is an enthusiastic, driven and goal oriented team player who has garnered over nine years of experience working in customer relations, administration and events planning. Not only is she meticulous, she is also excellent at juggling multiple tasks and working under pressure whilst adhering to strict deadlines.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Commercial Administrator (temporary role) Avonline, Bristol - 2023 (January-Present day)

## Responsibilities:

- Accurately checking and validating all data submitted by Sub-Contractors and sent in from the Commercial Team using a variety of Microsoft Excel Trackers and other systems
- Validating and creating summaries for Sub-Contractor weekly payments
- Liaising with Operations team to ensure all data is correctly captured with the sufficient evidence
- Support Commercial Team Lead with Application for Payments to the Client and reporting of Internal Revenue
- Regularly updating works progress trackers to ensure all works are being tracked and effectively carried out on time

Data Analyst (temporary role)
Lloyds Bank, Bristol - 2022 (June-December)

#### Responsibilities:

- Performing day to day administrative tasks including logging entries onto spreadsheets, updating customer database and processing and filing customer paperwork.
- Performing all tasks in compliance with banking policies and procedures whilst maintaining confidentiality of customer information.
- Ensuring completeness and accuracy of data entry and stored customer information in the database.

Administrative Assistant (temporary role) Channel 4, Bristol - 2022 (April-June)

## Responsibilities:

- Greeting guests and making them feel comfortable, both in person and over the phone.
- Maintaining front desk and verifying that orders are placed as necessary to ensure necessary supplies are available at all times.
- Directing guests to the appropriate departments.
- Taking deliveries, setting up meeting rooms.
- Alerting the management of potential security issues.
- Opening and closing the office.

# **Administrative Assistant/ Interpreter (temporary role)**

Fowlers, Bristol - Mar, 2021-Mar, 2022

# Responsibilities:

- Optimising the display of all goods.
- Greeting customers and dealing with enquiries.
- Processing payments and handling cash.
- Taking deliveries and ensuring Covid 19 safety guidelines were being followed.
- Interpreting and assisting on sales for Portuguese speaking customers.

## **Events Manager**

All Star Lanes, Brick Lane, London - Aug, 2019 - Sept, 2020

## Responsibilities:

- Booking reservations for customers, checking and redeeming deposits.
- Organising and hosting private events.
- Ensuring that events were properly serviced and refreshments were delivered within a timely manner.
- Organising, labelling and storing food in accordance to food safety standards.
- Processing payments and handling cash.
- Developed and maintained consistently solid, symbiotic relationships with several vendors.
- Acting as an interpreter for Portuguese speaking customers.

# **Bar Supervisor**

The Union Jack, Southwark, London - Mar, 2015-Aug, 2019

## Responsibilities:

- Responsible for the overall operations of the bar and supervising a small team to ensure a high level of service and masterful drink preparation.
- Communicating with vendors regarding back-order availability, future inventory and special orders.
- Acknowledging dedication to excellent customer service.
- Ensuring strict compliance to relevant health and safety standards within the bar.
- Assisting Portuguese speaking customers with their orders
- Cashdrawer maintenance.
- Serving customers.

#### **Bar Staff**

The Monarch, Camden Town, London - Sept,2014- Mar,2015

# Responsibilities:

- Working directly with customers by mixing and serving drink orders.
- Verifying age requirements, having good knowledge of alcohol pairings and standard drink recipes.
- Making accurate recommendations and answering questions from customers relating to drinks.
- Managing inventory and cleaning bar supplies.

Processing payments.

## **Club Hostess**

The Wellington Club, Knightsbridge, London - Oct,2013-Sept,2014

# Responsibilities:

- Anticipating customers' needs efficiently and quickly whilst maintaining tact and friendliness in a fast-paced environment.
- Ensuring that events were properly serviced and refreshments were served in a timely manner according to the events agendas.
- Waiting and clearing tables.
- Ensuring that relevant information was passed on to team leaders, supervisors and managers.

#### **Waitress**

Rodizio Rico, O2 Arena, London - Jan, 2013-Oct, 2013

## Responsibilities:

- Waiting tables in both Portuguese and english.
- Welcoming and seating guests.
- Taking guests' orders and communicating them effectively to the kitchen.
- Memorising the menus and offering recommendations to upsell appetisers, desserts and drinks.
- Processing payments on digital systems and handling cash.

## **CORE SKILLS**

- Knowledge of Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, Planner, Teams and PowerPoint.
- Good analytical skills.
- Excellent oral and written communication.
- Team player with an ability to work effectively with team members.
- Strong interpersonal skills.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Fluent English
Fluent Portuguese (native speaker)

## **EDUCATION**

Focus Fitness, London, UK - 2017 Level 3 Diploma in Personal Training

Instituto São Pio X, São Paulo, Brazil - 2010/2012 **4 A Levels** 

Instituto Santa Isabel, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil - 2010

Level 2 Certificate in General Patisserie and Confectionery

Instituto Santa Isabel, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil - 2009

Level 2 Award in Office Procedures

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST.